(Amy:)Well, I get why he's annoyed.
(Sheldon:)Well, then you don't
understand what's happening.
(Raj:)See...
(Sheldon:)Leonard refused to participate
(Sheldon:)in a mandatory quarterly
Roommate Agreement meeting.
(Sheldon:)This is what a generation raised
on Bart Simpson looks like.
You love The Simpsons.
(Sheldon:)I love Lisa Simpson.
(Amy:)Well, I know how he feels.
(Amy:)I never enjoyed our
Relationship Agreement meetings.
(gasps) Wait.
(Sheldon:)You were pretending?
(Raj:)Sorry.
No!
(Sheldon:)I don't believe you.
I could tell.
"Oh, Sheldon,
"I never thought
"re-filing a matter
(Amy:)in a standing subcommittee
could be so fascinating."
(Sheldon:)Hmm, what do you think?
(Penny:)You don't know?